Well, everybody, welcome to NFA live.
Looks like the inflation data is out and
it is not too awful.
So, to help me break that down, I've got
Guy from Coin Bureau and Coin Finance
and Coin Korea and Coin Everything.
Thank you, Guy, for stopping by.
And Ben into the cryptoverse. How's How
are you guys doing? How you doing, Guy?
>> Yeah, I'm well, thanks, Rob. I'm well.
I've had a couple of weeks back home in
the UK and now, uh, back home again in
Dubai. So, uh, yeah, it's all good.
>> All good. And Ben, after 2 weeks off,
how things been for you?
>> Good. Just, um, yeah, was out of town
for the last week on, uh, vacation, so
feel pretty good. Bitcoin's the same
price as I left it, so here we are.
>> See, this is why you left it and you let
it go just chop sideways and that's
fine.
So, everybody, before we get into it,
I'd like to remind everybody that, uh,
there's a little conference going on in
Miami, 20th to the 22nd of November.
And we've got, uh, quite a few people
who are speaking. There's this guy named
Ben.
And, uh, Kim Markeyusko, Alessio
Rastani, James Check, which I got to
tell you, that guy puts out some really
good information. I'd like to hear what
he has to say. Mike McGlone, this guy
named Guy Turner,
Gareth David, Jason Pizzino, even Al Do,
FA?
Kamichi, Crypto Kid, Tom Crown and Matt
Crosby rounding it all out. So, like I
said before, I think everybody deserves
a vacation after this brutal brut- well,
not so bear market. So, join us in
Miami. Should be a fun time. And just so
you know, pricing for the tickets are
due to go up at some point, but good
news for you today,
if you're watching this video,
you have a chance to win a couple of
tickets. So, there's a link in the
description. Fill out this form and at
the end of this live stream, we're going
to
add or pick some people at random
for two basic standards and one pro
today. And just so we keep everything
even and we know that this isn't rigged
like all other elections, I'll be
putting this into a nice little
little picker that's Claude drew up for
me. All right, everybody. So, that would
be the shameless plug for the
conference. Let's get into the numbers.
So, this just came out
what 30 minutes ago or so. Looks like
Well, first of all, yesterday
Wash came out and said that he is not
raising rates,
but there's a couple of uh
members of the team
that looks like they're dissenting. I'll
talk to Guy about that. But right now
we've got PC price index for June. It
fell 0.1%.
So, that's great.
Month-over-month stood at 3.7
year-over-year. The core PC price index
increased 0.1, so kind of like a wash.
GDP grew at an annualized rate of 1.5%
and initial jobless claims at 197,000.
I think that's a pretty low numbers.
We'll take a look at it.
And the market has responded. Looks like
Bitcoin likes that. Let me refresh this
real quick.
Last hour or so, so not too bad.
And
let's break this down and get into it.
But first I want to ask Guy. Guy, you
put out a nice little snippet here
on short. You talked about three things
that Wash came out and said that were
concerning. So, tell us about that.
And then we'll break down a little bit
of the economic macro with Ben. But what
were the three things that you talked
about here?
>> Yeah, sure. And remember of course this
is you know, this is Kevin Wash very
very much has a very different attitude
to what the Fed you know, what the Fed
should be saying and doing.
Especially as as it concerns you know,
forward guidance and stuff. So, um,
yeah, I mean the the third sort of thing
that he said was, uh, you know, that the
Fed is is very much focused on forcing
inflation down to that 2% target, no
matter the cost. Um, and it was
interesting what he he said around this.
He said that, you know, five years of
high prices have made made people accept
>> 3% as
as normal.
Um, so, you know, it's it's kind of this
this idea of shifting baseline theory,
you know. People are kind of getting
used to 3% inflation now, whereas
actually, you know, the Fed's mandate is
a whole percentage lower than that, and
that's what they should be aiming at.
Um, and he also said, um, there are no
soft targets. So, what he meant by that
was that he will that the Fed will keep
rates high enough, um, until they have,
uh, an effect of an effect on inflation,
until they bring inflation down,
even if, you know, that causes that
causes pain, you know, that hurts, um,
that hurts family budgets or or
whatever. Because I think, you know, he,
like many others, recognizes just how
insidious a force inflation is, and you
you know, you have to stay on top of it.
So,
I think that's something to bear in
mind. You know, and and it's kind of,
you know, it's it's it's it's it's it's
along the same sort of lines as what
Powell would always say as well. Um, but
I guess that shows that, you know, one
thing hasn't changed from from the
transition in in chair, and that's still
the idea that 2% is the inflation
target, and that is what inflation needs
to be at, um, no matter no matter the
cost.
Um, and then and then and that kind of
leads on to the second thing he said
that, you know, interest rates could
actually go up. As we as you mentioned,
Rob, three [snorts] members of that
12-person FOMC board dissented, and
their dissent was they wanted to raise
rates right now. Um, and the phrase, uh,
that was used was, um, that this is the
beginning of the story and not the end.
So, you know, that means for anyone
who's got, you know, carrying debt or
hoping that mortgage rates are going to
go down or whatever, you know, sorry.
That isn't going to happen. So, the
specter of rate rises is still very much
alive and I think it's probably, you
know, a question of sooner rather than
later. Um
but the the first one was perhaps more
concerning than the other two and that
is, you know, again, this feeds into
what Kevin Warsh has been saying kind of
ever since he took the reins, is that
they're not going to do forward
guidance. They're not going to give any
early warnings, um you know, about what
they're they won't give any hints about
what they're going to do. Um and the
phrase he used, you know, to investors
was to play the ball and not the
referee, um which I which [laughter] I
quite liked.
>> That's pretty good.
>> I like that.
>> good.
Um I I like to think that's a nice
football analogy, um you know, in time
just for the end of the World Cup. Um
so, but you know, what this means is
that without the sort of early warnings,
without that forward guidance that we
were used to under Powell, it means that
everything, you know, all investors, all
markets, everyone, um the smart money,
the dumb money and everyone in between
is just left guessing until the actual
decision is announced. And of course,
that means uncertainty and that means
volatility. Um so, it's kind of making
it's kind of making it very tricky to
get an idea of where they might be
headed. Um we obviously have tools out
there, you know, the FedWatch and what
have you,
but yeah, with the lack of forward
guidance, it very much becomes a bit of
a guessing game until we know it. So,
yeah, that makes it that makes it that
little bit harder.
>> I think so. Well said, guy. Well said.
And then talking about those tools, we
can see here that this was I didn't
refresh my my browser. I want to leave
this here. The target rate 353.75, they
called it, they nailed it. I I think a
lot of people said that they were not
going to raise rates. Watch was going to
stay the same. The only one that said
that it would actually might happen was
Citadel Securities, which I thought was
kind of interesting, as they came out
and said, "Yeah, it's going to be a
surprise raise. You guys just watch and
see." And of course, the numbers don't
lie. However, taking a look here, the
next meeting we have is coming up on
16th of September 2026. And just like
what you said, Guy, uh we've got three
dissenters. We can see that uh the rates
looks like they would be going up 375 to
400. Let me refresh that. Maybe things
have changed a little bit. Who knows?
Eh, a little bit. But, it's a 60/40
split. It looks like we might raise
rates. So, this would come back to Ben.
What do you think here? If we start to
raise rates and we start to talk about
this and that expectation is coming in
into the markets. I did like this video
you put out. This was your last one.
Well, when will the Fed raise rates? And
he had a nice
uh overlay. And you took a look at the
inflation uh year-over-year. And you
took also a look at the uh two-year
Treasuries as they are lining up. But,
the two-year Treasury, which the Fed has
been tracking, you talked about how this
is actually increased.
And this is where you think that the Fed
rates will actually go as they will
increase. So, as you see the numbers
that are there, what's your thoughts
here, Ben, moving forward?
>> Yeah, um
back in
what, like last or earlier this year,
the Fed funds rate was lower than the
two-year yield.
Uh but, that's now changed. It's now
higher than the two-year yield. And so,
what that what that sort of means is if
you believe in the neutral rate, this
abstract concept,
from which when the Fed funds rate is
above the two-year yield, the argument
is that we are in restrictive territory
in terms of monetary policy. And when
it's below, it's more accommodative. So,
earlier this year, and you know, for the
last year or two, the Fed funds rate has
been above the two-year yield, I
believe.
But, that's changed now. And and so, you
could argue that while it was above it,
there was this you could pretty clearly
see higher-risk assets bleeding to
lower-risk assets. That's why things
like Bitcoin dominance were going up and
whatnot.
But, now it's flipped back, right? Now
it's flipped back and the two-year yield
is is actually above the Fed funds rate,
even though the Fed funds rate hasn't
gone anywhere in a while. So, the
argument now is that because the neutral
rate is a moving target, the
you we're no longer in restrictive
territory. And if that's the case, then,
you know, the labor market might start
to heat back up again. You can already
see the unemployment rate has been
trending down, initial claims have been
trending down. That could put pressure
on wage inflation, which could put
pressure on overall inflation, headline
inflation.
And so, I think what you're seeing
happen
is the Fed's unwilling to raise rates,
and now the bond market is revolting.
You know, if you look at the 30-year
yield, it's breaking out to new highs,
the 10-year yield's probably heading
back up to where it was in October 2023.
When yields were breaking out, starting
in July, they started to really move up
in July 2023 until October of 2023, the
S&P ended up getting like a 10% drop.
So,
I think that we are likely going to get
a rate hike this year. I don't know
exactly what month. I mean, September
seems like a a likely candidate, but I
think you will have one. And and then I
think people are going to get really
spooked by it because, you know, a rate
hike
after rate cuts kind of hits a little
bit different than just a rate hike, you
know, kind of
a few years ago. Um
but, I I think it would be kind of a the
perfect narrative for everything playing
out just the way it always does, right?
Like the stock market gets a correction
in the back half of the midterm year,
Bitcoin finds a market cycle bottom, and
it's all because people are freaking out
about the Fed's raising rates, and all,
you know, what's what's going to happen
now. Um, so I think it I think if you
need a narrative, it's there. Not that
you need one.
>> [laughter]
>> We all need a narrative. That's the
whole thing. We we appreciate those. So,
right now, we can see that uh this is
essentially where we are at. I still
think that we're going to see a little
bit of uh of uh rate hikes, and even I
think one of the one of the Fed uh Oh,
no, the
one of the Fed members was on Squawk Box
yesterday.
Uh, I forget his name, but he talked
about and he was the most dovish person.
He said, "Even I can see a case for
raising rates." So, if people are
expecting things to just keep dropping,
I don't think it's actually going to
happen. So, evaluate that and put that
into your
uh your buying or selling strategy. I
think we've got a little bit of a rocky
road going into and out of the midterm
years.
So, thank you, gentlemen, for that. I
just wanted to see where we were
actually at with macro.
And that would uh really conclude the
macro part. The next part we're going to
talk about before we get into the
drawing
is just an anecdotal story.
And I like this one because uh it kind
of shows you where where things are at.
Now, if you're a technical trader, this
has nothing to do with, but I got to
tell you this was a pretty good one. I
had a I lunched with a friend last week,
and he talked about how he sold his
truck.
He's a farmer.
Sold his truck, and he was going to put
it all into Bitcoin. But, you This guy's
a little bit different. He was in a
Bitcoin in 2013,
and he's been holding for quite some
time and had some pretty good gains, and
um
yeah, he's doing not too bad, I think.
But, he sold his truck.
He took a loan out to buy another truck
cuz he's a farmer and needs that.
And uh
and I and he says he goes, "I'm going to
buy Bitcoin this week." He just bought
recently.
So, my question to you, and uh guy, I'll
start with you. Do you think this was a
was a good move for him to do in in the
long run or the short run? Or you think
this was just uh crazy talk? And then,
what do you hear about as far as like
people around you and the sentiment for
crypto right now? Bitcoin specific.
>> Yeah.
So
So he sold the truck. So he he now
>> He now does not have a truck.
>> No, no, no. So he sold his truck. He got
55K out of it. It's a very nice truck,
Ford F-150, one of my favorites.
And uh he took that 55K and dumped it
into Bitcoin. lump sum
>> Okay.
>> And then he's like a loan out to buy
another truck cuz he needs a new truck.
He's like, I'd like to get a new truck
anyhow. So he's got a loan
at whatever it is, I don't even know,
6.5% something like that over 5 years.
So would this be like a good strategy
for him to do or this is just uh crazy
talk?
>> Well, I yeah, I just wanted to check
because I mean so he's not without a
truck at the moment cuz as you say he's
a farmer and he needs one. So he has he
has got a truck. He's just rotated some
of the money that he made on the last
one out of it. Okay.
>> Exactly.
>> Okay. Well, that was good cuz if he if
he was without a truck, I was going to
say he's the biggest fool alive. But
that's good. Okay.
Um
Yeah, I mean I I don't love the idea of
>> [clears throat]
>> however well you're doing, I don't love
the idea of taking out a loan to buy
well
to buy anything really. But you know, a
speculate a highly speculative and very
volatile asset like Bitcoin. You know,
taking out a loan to buy that is not
something I would ever advise anyone to
do. Even though I believe that in the
long term uh Bitcoin will start going
back up again and I'm I'm kind of on
board with what Ben said about, you
know, the
the way the cycle playing out and uh
possibly towards the end of this year,
you know, we could see um we could see
prices start to rise again.
So I guess on that timeline, he's he's
bought it a good time. But, like I say,
I feel very uncomfortable with the idea
that he's done it with borrowed money.
Um because I kind of feel you know, I
kind of feel he's sort of Okay, he was
in it in 2013, made a nice profit out of
it.
You know, what because you won last time
doesn't necessarily mean you'll win
again. So, all you know, I've got to
hope that he's got other ways of paying
that loan back if Bitcoin doesn't do
what he wants to do because I I think
getting in debt to buy a highly risky
speculative asset like Bitcoin is is not
is not the way forward personally.
>> Well, yeah, I can see that for sure. And
remember like it's it's for for some
people would I remember this happened in
2021.
Where people would take out massive
loans and go into all coins and just
lose everything.
And when he did it, it was just
interesting to me because he has a
another stream of revenue, which is he
has real estate, he has crops and things
like that. So, he's like, "Look, I just
wanted this to come in and I just
thought it was an interesting story and
a different timing." Cuz he talked about
how he did a big a big move in 2018 as
well when Bitcoin was at $3,000.
And he said it worked out pretty well.
So, we'll see how it works. I just
wanted to put this story out cuz I want
to reference this in the next 2 3 years
or so and see where we're actually at
and if 60,000 was an awful mistake or a
pretty good strategy. We'll see.
>> Oh, man. I mean, I I really hope it
works out for him cuz that would be That
would be amazing. You know, if it goes
if it goes to 200K or whatever and he
you know, quadruples his money or
whatever it is, great. I really
>> [laughter]
>> I really hope that turns out to be the
case.
But,
you know, um I guess it kind of it kind
of suggests to me that we live very much
in that sort of culture now where I you
know, I don't think there there is a
gambling element to it, but it just
seems like so many people are just like
to hell with it. I'm just going to I'm
going to spin that wheel. I'm going to
take that risk. And I think that says a
lot about the world we live in and you
know, the the the the values that we
have. Um but yeah, I mean I think
>> [clears throat]
>> now you hear a story like that and most
people are like, you know, they might be
like me and it's like, well, it's not a
great idea, but I think most people
would be like, okay, good luck to you.
Whereas if you'd said that to someone 30
years ago,
>> [laughter]
>> you know, they'd be like, what?
The guy's insane.
Um so yeah, we the world has changed a
lot.
>> 30 years ago people would say, you know
what you need to do? Collect a pension
and then just put everything away in
your savings account, you'll be just
fine.
Anyhow,
Ben, last question. Last question for
you. What do you think about that that
strategy? Would you ever do something
like that? It seems kind of crazy right
now.
>> I mean I think um probably depends on
his timeline, right? Like if he's if his
timeline's long enough, it probably
works out. If it's not, probably
doesn't. You know I
one of my
someone I
you know, learned from a long time ago,
he would tell me about like with stocks
and stuff, like don't ever buy don't
ever buy the S&P unless, you know,
unless you are have the ability to hold
it for at least a few years. Like if you
if you're going to buy it
and like it has to go to a certain price
or it can't go down in like the next 6
months or something and you're buying
it, you're probably better off not
buying it. But if you can hold it for,
you know, I mean I think with the stock
market and it was like 5 or 10 years,
then there's no reason to worry that
much about like what the stock market's
going to do next month. So, I mean I
think with Bitcoin, obviously, there's
this 4-year cycle stuff looming over our
heads and and, you know, sort of um
would say that the price could go lower,
but at the same time normally just
buying Bitcoin in the second half of the
midterm year works out relatively well
as long as cuz can like not panic um
if there is that if there is that drop
in key for I mean I typically prefer to
DCA in
to Bitcoin um
>> [clears throat]
>> rather than rather than lump sum just
because
I mean you know the stock market doesn't
drop usually like 50% overnight whereas
we've seen Bitcoin do that many times.
Um
so it's a little bit different you know
than than investing in the stock market.
So I mean I hope it works out for him.
Um
probably going to be you know maybe some
a few more scary times this year before
hopefully things are things look a
little bit better.
>> Yep, well said. So we'll see how it all
works out. I'd like to reference this
story as time goes on because it's
always interesting to get that
perspective especially as we are in the
bear market midterm lows.
And that's it for today everybody. So if
you'd like today's video, thumbs up,
subscribe, all that great stuff. There's
a link to to Ben's channel and Guy's
channels plural. You can check those
out. Now let's get into the last part
which would be draw and giveaway. So
everybody
thanks so much for
putting in the information
to attend the conference. I'll be there,
Guy will be there. This will be the
first time we've all been together in
the same place. It's kind of strange.
So maybe we'll do an NFA live like
really live.
So you filled this out already. Let's
see who we got. All right. I'm not going
to show everybody's email because that
would be a tragic error.
But let me just do this. I'm going to
take all the first names.
Uh
uh
>> [clears throat]
>> ta-da
and
>> Rob, you're awfully dressed up today.
>> Yeah, you know.
I try to I try to make a good impression
on some people. Try to
>> I might be a little bit decent.
>> Yeah, well, you got Ben when you got 10
kids, you know, it's ain't easy. You got
to do all those things that you got.
Let's see. So,
I'm going to put these names in.
And we're going to draw three winners.
Uh remove dupli- Actually, no, no, no.
Yeah, let's do three winners. The last
winner
will be the one for the higher tier.
Uh I forgot what it's called. The Ben
has it at the pro tier.
So, let's draw those winners. We're
going to remove the duplicate entries. I
know some of you tried to cheat. And if
you ain't cheating, you ain't trying, so
good job.
Winner one, Dylan, David, and Anthony.
So, I have your names. Let me do a
screenshot of that.
I will be emailing you personally from
my account, and I will be asking you for
one Bitcoin, and I will send you two
back. Obviously not. So, expect those
emails to be coming out. And again,
everybody, those will be the last
drawing for the ITC conference. Again,
I'd like to see everybody there, as many
people as we can to get there. We got
some pretty good uh speakers. So, uh
let's all hang out in Miami. And that's
it for this part. Now, let's go into a
little Q&A session. You can ask Guy and
Ben anything,
and they'll answer all your questions,
and then we'll get the heck out of here.
All right. So, what do we have?
Congrats, winners. There's no one left.
>> There's dozens of us left, Rob.
>> There's
>> [laughter]
>> Exactly.
There's only so many. Congrats to all
the winners. I always hated that. Like
like when I would like like lose in
sports, I'd like, "Yeah,
congratulations." But you don't really
really really mean it. You're like,
"Damn it, I could have won that one."
Thank you.
Oh, Gas Safety says no ladies as
speakers.
This is
What's What's the next
>> we're we're probably announcing a couple
like in the next week that are that are
women actually.
>> Mhm.
>> It's not my fault. It's just that they
the people we just haven't had as in a
line up, but I think we have some now.
>> Very nice. Hello from Maldives selling
tickets.
Huh.
Uh
Well, what's your Well, HyperLiquid?
This is one of the few altcoins that
actually
went up and it had a nice ROI. What's
your thoughts on HYPE? Guy, I think
you're more of the altcoin person as
opposed to say banning derivatives. So
>> Yeah, I mean, I think I think it's been
sort of struggling a little bit
recently. There does seem to be a bit
more competition. I think lighter is is
maybe giving HyperLiquid a bit of a run
for its money. But, I mean, it is still
it is still very much the venue
especially for kind of out of hours
trading, isn't it? I mean, like the you
know, this Iran this Iran conflict it's
sort of I think it was a big kind of
proving thing, you know, because when
when stuff was happening out of hours
and people were able to speculate on oil
and what have you.
But, you know, I've certainly of of the
major altcoin projects, it's one of the
it's one of the few that has that's
found sort of product market fit. People
love it. It generates a ton of revenue.
I mean, I think I saw somewhere, you
know, HyperLiquid alone is responsible
for the
you know, if not the majority then
certainly a huge chunk of overall app
revenue in crypto, which shows us that
we've got a long way to go. But, I yeah,
I think it's and and of course they're
doing I think they're still doing
buybacks of HYPE
>> Yeah.
>> So
I don't see why unless something unless
something bad happened unless it gets
hacked or has some sort of exploit or
something like that, I think it's going
to I think it's going to stick around. I
I know Lewis, my
colleague here at Coin Bureau,
has has said that he's going to buy a
whole lot more of it if it
What did he say? He's investing $5,000
into Hype every time it drops 10%.
Um
so, you know, there's some there's some
conviction for you. But yeah, I I think
I think long term Hype should should do
well.
>> Very nice. Yeah, I got a little bit of
that. Hopefully it does well. How about
this one? What's the chances
percentage-wise that the bottom is
already in for Bitcoin?
Anyone want to take that one? Bottom
already in, I think we got some time to
go, but that's me.
>> I mean, I think anything's possible.
Like you you can't ever ever get too
confident in, you know, a low being
either in or not.
I would say it's probably less than 50%
would be my guess that it's already in.
I I think the most likely time is the
fourth quarter of the year. Um that's
that's what it normally is.
Um and I I think the hard thing about
this year is like the you know, like the
constant mental gymnastics around that.
Like
>> Yeah.
>> And and even back in like early this
year when we were talking about how
Bitcoin
>> coin usually finds a low in February and
then bounces, people are like, "Oh, no,
just cuz it usually does that, this
time's going to be different." And then
it did the same thing anyways, right?
And then in May, we even did a we I
think we did a
like a live stream. I think you I think
Rob titled it like sell in May and go
away and how Bitcoin then normally sells
off again in the summer and people are
like, "No, just that just cuz it always
happens, it doesn't mean it will happen
again." And then it just happened again
anyways. So, like I I I it's not like I
don't understand where people are coming
from, but
I'm also of the opinion if it's not
broke, don't fix it, you know? So, like,
"Hey, if the market wants to prove me
wrong, let it prove me wrong." Until
then, I'm I'm just going to assume it's
going to keep doing what it always does.
>> Yeah, I think so. Guy, same thing or?
>> Yeah. Yeah, not much to add there. I
agree. Yeah.
>> It's It's a funny I think we live in the
matrix. It seemed like things just keep
going round about almost Groundhog Day
like, but we'll see.
Uh here's a good one and it's a it's a
question I actually have. What's the
reason strategy is not buying the lows?
I don't really understand. Strategy does
a great job of buying the the the tops,
that's for sure.
And also selling
selling some of the bottoms.
But
anything you guys are tracking over
there at Coin Bureau guy?
>> Well, I just think that strategy's been
kind of very much caught out by the fact
that that I think they just
over-leveraged isn't the word, I don't
think. But they I think they could just
got too ambitious, you know,
issuing
issuing things like stretch, this STRC
preferred stock or whatever that pays a
pretty hefty dividend.
And giving themselves these obligations
to meet, you know, these dividend
obligations to meet etc.
Which means they have to have cash or
you know, you know, they they have to
find a way of raising cash. And either
they do that by diluting MSTR holders,
which is what they've been mostly doing,
or selling Bitcoin, which they've done,
you know, they did a little bit of it
and the market really did not like that
at all.
Um, so I guess, you know, probably the
plan was to keep on accumulating through
the lows if you know, unless they just
mis-timed the lows. But
yeah, I think I think basically they've
their strategy was um, you know,
overcomplicated, a bit ambitious.
Just buy just buy and buy and hold
Bitcoin. But instead, you know, they
they found this so-called infinite money
glitch. And guess what? It didn't quite
work out like that. And now the market
is basically telling them, "No, you're
you can't go and buy more
Bitcoin right now because you need to
have cash on hand in order to honor
those dividend obligations and
everything else. Um, otherwise people
are going to people are going to, you
know, dump MSTR, people are going to
lose faith in Bitcoin or whatever." So I
think kind of that they've they've had
their hand forced in a way is my best
guess.
>> So it's one more one more reason why
treasury companies will bleed the
Bitcoin over the long term in my
opinion.
>> Yeah, unfortunately so. And I have to
apologize. I I thought that they bought
the high, but they did not. They bought
it 117k, so I stand corrected. All
right. So, let's see what else we have.
Uh
This is a good one. Ben, there's not
enough gold stars available for you. You
excel as a human being. Thank you very
very much for all your hard work. It is
such a dichotomy, such a difference
between like the live streams of what's
being said about Ben as opposed to like
on X and what's being said about Ben.
It's like Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde. It's
amazing to me every time.
>> Yeah. No, I mean it's been like a
Imagine Imagine how I I mean I don't
really
I don't really feel
um a lot of emotions towards comments
anymore on X, but man, like three, four
years ago they I mean I would just like
a bucket of misery like like listening
to these reading these comments that
people would say about me. And then And
then now I look back and I'm like, "No,
I I I I'm happy that I said what I said
back then." And and you know, I'm I'm
not going to apologize for it.
>> Yeah.
See,
you just got to take just take a take a
page out of Guy Guy's book. You just
post great information constantly over
at Coin Bureau. It's always like good
stuff just about the news, just the
facts, ma'am, and that's it. And there's
very like like little little back and
forth.
All right.
I think that's Yeah, I think that's it.
Hater is hard of hearing.
Meta planets. I think we
I'm the same way. The digital asset
treasuries, especially for Ethereum,
oof.
Pretty brutal. We'll see if that goes
through.
>> Well, look at some Jack Mallers. He just
stepped away from 21, didn't he? There
was a There was a British one that I
never heard of called Satsuma or
something like that. Just wound wound it
up. I'm sure there will be more. I'm
sure there will be more because it's
it's the sort of thing like it can work
for, you know, it can work for one. I
think I I think strategy will be fine.
Um you know, they've had their they've
they've had their wings clipped a little
bit, but they'll be okay.
Um but all these smaller ones, I mean,
it was a it was an accident. It was a
disaster waiting to happen. So, you
know, the sooner the sooner they just
the sooner the crap ones just go and die
and, you know, put all their Bitcoin
back on the market so as so as, you
know, other people can accumulate it the
better, really.
>> So, that's spoken like a a a true
multi-cycle veteran. All right,
everybody. That's it for today. If you
like today's video, thumbs up,
subscribe, all that good stuff. Links in
the description for everything. Again,
we'll see you guys in November, all
three of us, in Miami.
Thanks so much, everybody. See you on
the next one. Adios.
>> Yep.
See you.